this is [ __ ] I don't want to spend
another day at the bitch I want to be at
home playing video games not watching
your uncle shucks lather more sunscreen
on his smelly butt cheeks come on dude
we had so much fun yesterday
listen cracker the only fun I had
yesterday was when I took a poop in the
ocean and nobody noticed I'm going to
make like diarrhea and run catch you
guys on the flip side sorry we're late
everyone
Mandy needed some help fitting into her
swimsuit here my boobs are like monster
trucks in the small bikini hahaha you
know maybe coming back out here wasn't
such a bad idea
God damn
[Music]
[ __ ] [ __ ] those are some nice butt
cheeks hey Sonia nice boobies oh I mean
nice day today isn't it
haha Oh Knuckles you're so funny it's
it's not like I wanted to grab your
[ __ ] boobies or anything haha oh Knox
you silly you hey what can I say us
Jamaicans are crazy as [ __ ] hahaha help
with sunscreen what was that dude
why the hell are you acting like such a
[ __ ] damn you're sick checking out my big
fat ass what the hell's your problem man
now go climb up that tree over there and
get some coconuts Robotnik bet me like
20 bucks that he could crush one between
his thighs okay um just smell that
tropical air it's so quaint and rustic I
agree this place is a whole lot earlier
than your pool at home but I'm having a
lot of fun well that's the only thing
that matters isn't it come now Beach
let's join the others it appears
somebody is making an announcement
attention attention everyone please be
quiet for just one minute the hell do
you want
yeah Rhea pants we Tito your women evil
man I'm glad you asked now if you would
all take a look at the pamphlet I handed
out this morning
go on now I made sure that everyone one
of you got one
so no lying [ __ ] do you hear me
what you see before you is the special
bonding activity that I scheduled for
today's event
I call it robotics badasses and castle
competition I thought it would add some
healthy competition so everybody split
up into teams of two well there's an odd
amount of us so I guess the one sad
lonely [ __ ] all alone will have to be
the judge haha oh I see you're all
already forming into your teams hey
Charles remember yesterday you want to
be on my team oh I see you already have
a partner no it's fine I'll ask someone
else
pace Leto I see you have a partner also
hey Manik my [ __ ] the teams have been
decided from here on out you put all
your trust in your partner because no
one wants to be with me
i Robotnik will be the judge and now let
us begin the first annual Robotnik's
badass sandcastle building competition
you go Manic I'm rooting for you sugar
beet quick the guys
Knuckles take your gloves off all of the
sand is sticking to them like goop
sticks to toilet paper now don't worry
about it bro it's all good no it isn't
[ __ ] look all of the sand it's sticking
to a your glove it's ruining everything
take them off how about you shut it
greenbean talk me like that again and
your heads going in my butt crack do you
understand
white boy hey Knuckles can I ask you
something yeah man
shoot what's up what exactly are those
spikes on your gloves like are they part
of your head like some deformity or some
[ __ ] are you for real as if I got these
gloves on Craigslist
the calls they make me look like a
[ __ ] bad-ass no one wants to mess
with a guy who wears these bad boys well
so those spikes on your hands are just a
part of your gloves haha of course they
are don't [ __ ] here take a look see my
hand is the same as yours
Charles I picked you out as my partner
but calls you our fellow man men know
how to build things it is in our nature
to do hard labor then go home and [ __ ]
our [ __ ]
er eh I know and that's why I am leaving
the design of our sandcastle to you
whatever you want to make I will do what
is in my power to make your idea into a
reality which yo say what we made our
way it isn't so much an idea Woodmoor yo
[ __ ] it on 22 tobias and costly
buta sculptor a sculptor e of their own
hol of a in believer the only one ever
left me see they meet email of Ned and
was al Weiss today who AM prima donna
Heather their most that is what even NOx
emission costly and Danny chill call
create a boutonniere equal passe on a
widow interest Antalya spookiness
gloriosa machi read in front of tessen
bullet this which is teh foking teeth
know where Emily already found some even
a solution show curry asan is a call
cannot read delete whose your watchman
is you make it a most badass monolith of
public this world has ever seen
Charles your vision is worthy of even
the toughest men I will try
no I will make this the best sandcastle
ever even if my life depended on it
you
he kindled it all very clear we are
sorry about that I kind of accidentally
took a dump on so I tried to remake it
in my image instead
hey guys is that your sandcastle not
half-bat might even be runner-up for
second place but what is it supposed to
be you see that seashell that represents
a sexy woman with big boobs she is
making bologna sandwiches to serve to
the man which is signified by the candy
wrapper
it's the never-ending cycle that woman
are beneath us waiting on hand and foot
in the kitchen oh well what's that
crushed bear can over in the corner for
not in Ryoji a host a lucky queer and
primero couldent fin de rebecca can do
you know how we're going to decorate the
sandcastle here yay I'm gonna make it
look just like Barbie's Dreamhouse that
sounds like fun
look here's a pretty seashell right here
now where should I put this maybe right
no oh okay well maybe over here then no
not there either
stop it don't you know anything about
Barbie's Dreamhouse you dumb [ __ ]
hey hey [ __ ] what's the prize for first
place prizes there are no prizes damn it
Sonia let's just stop we can't do that
what about the competition do you really
want to be a quitting [ __ ]
Sonia your brother and his boyfriend
Barca be made a complete recreation of
the lost city of Atlantis Robotnik
already gave them the trophy and went
home
Barnaby hired the three best artists in
the entire world to make it in like five
minutes this competition was over before
it even began hey Beach do you see that
Island over there you mean the coast of
Australia yeah I bought that Oh Bart
levy I had so much fun today thank you
so much for spending time with me and
this amazing sandcastle I couldn't have
done it without you no Beach it is I who
must thank you for having such a big ass
[Music]
[Applause]